Hello friends, in today's video I am going to
tell you
how you can get personal accident insurance. Before that, let me
tell you that if you don't know what
personal accident insurance is, then let me
tell you, for example, suppose you have a family, one of
your family members is
earning and travels by bike every day, and suppose
while traveling by bike, he has an
accident,
he dies or someone gets injured
badly, if you have personal
accident insurance, then here
you will get some money from the insurance company, so
this is friends, personal
accident insurance and I am going to tell you that it is very cheap,
no, it is an insurance of ₹40
which is given here on the phone,
so in today's video I will
tell you how you
can get it, so let's learn how
you can get accident insurance of ₹40
here, so friends, for this,
first of all you have to come on your phone
and scroll down here, you can
see it in the insurance section here.  There is an option here for personal
accident, click here,
if the option is not coming then click on the seal and it will
come here, let's
click here, as soon as you
click, you can see that there is a
lot of insurance here, first of all let's
talk about it, but it is of ₹40,
friends, you just have to pay those ₹40 and
after that, if all these insurances are for one year,
friends, they are
with a validity of one year, if you want, you
can also increase the feature of that ₹40,
if you insure something,
during an accident within a year, then
your family will get one
lakh, there you will get 5 lakh in 195,
10 lakh in 30 and here
you can get up to 20 lakh rupees in 780, if we
talk about the most popular, then friends,
suppose something happens to the person in whose name the insurance is,
during an accident, you will
get 1 crore rupees here, so for that, there is a plan in place, in the name of the person in
whose name it is.
Its monthly insurance should be at least 1 lakh rupees
and in the 50 lakh one it should be
₹50, there is
no criteria for the rest, if you want, you can
take insurance here for just seven rupees, that is, anyone.
First of all, let me tell you that
if something happens to the person in whose name the insurance is, only then
your family will get the money, otherwise someone
else's, that is, suppose if insurance is in your name
and someone else has an
accident, then it is not that
he will get it, that is, if something happens to the person in whose name the insurance is,
then you will
get it here, so let's click on the thirty nine one,
click on get policy here, as if you click here, you
can see here, the complete details will
come here, sum insurance 1 lakh rupees,
validity one year, here you have to enter your name,
enter your email ID and keep in
mind here that enter the email ID correctly, the complete document
of the policy will be sent to the email ID which you enter, but the
complete document of the policy i.e. insurance will be sent to that email ID from the phone side
I will send you the document, after that you have to enter the date of
birth here and after that accept the terms and
conditions and pay, so let me
enter the email ID here, you can see
friends, I have
entered the complete details here, accept the terms and conditions here
and click on here,
like click on here, if you want, you can
direct here if you use it on the phone then you
can do it here or you
can make the payment only with the help of add UPA,
then if your birth certificate
is a credit card then now by adding it here you
can see, you can also pay those ₹40 with credit card or debit card,
but if
you use it on the phone then you
can also pay directly from the phone, so as if I
click on paper here, our insurance will be done
here, but I was making this video only
for you so that you can
get the complete details and in this way you
can take insurance, so you just have to
click on and ₹40 will be deducted and in
this way you can get personal accident
insurance, so I hope
you  You will like the video. If you like the video then
please like the video and subscribe to the channel and if you have any doubt then please comment and
reply.